SFU Archives reference and display materials collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Portraits, [ca 1960] - 2002; F-247-1; 1.55 m of textual records 1254 photographs 412 contact sheets 137 negatives 56 slides
  - Psychology, 1966 - 1976; F-247-1-15; 2 cm of textual records 14 photographs 19 contact sheets 1 negative
    - Ingling, Jane, 1966; F-247-1-15-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Kendall, L.M., 1966; F-247-1-15-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Koopman, R.F., 1966; F-247-1-15-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Lyman, B.E., 1966; F-247-1-15-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Smith, W.A. Samuel; Dean of Arts, 1966 - 1976; F-247-1-15-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: SF Week: June 17, 1976.
    - Wilson, Lolita, 1966; F-247-1-15-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: Audio Visual Centre.
  - Science, 1966 - 1990; F-247-1-16; 6 photographs 8 contact sheets
    Sub-series consists of photos of individuals from the Faculty of Science. For a list of faculty members associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Webster, John M.; Faculty of Science
    - Webster, John; Dean of Science; Assistant VP Academic; Dean of Graduate Studies, 1969 - 1990; F-247-1-16-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 81009-12, M&PR.
    - Faculty and Staff (contact sheets), 1966 - 1969; F-247-1-16-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC, Helcermanas.
  - Biological Sciences, 1965 - 1990; F-247-1-17; 4 cm of textual records 55 photographs 28 contact sheets 2 negatives
    Sub-series consists of photos, articles, and published material relating to individuals from the Department of Biological Sciences. For a list of faculty members associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Barlow, John S.; Beirne, Bryan P.; Brooke, R.C.; Finlayson, Thelma; Fisher, F.J. Fulton; Geen, Glen H.; Glen, I.R.; Haver, Stoner; Mackauer, J.P.M.; Nair, Karun K.; Nelson, C. Donald; Sadleir, R.M.; Srivastava, Lalit M.; Schwarz, Abby; Turnbull, Albert; Turner, John; VanEerton, G.; VanOverbeek, A.P.; Vidaver, Bill; Department of Biological Sciences
    - Barlow, Jack, [ca 1969]; F-247-1-17-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: Ron Long, LIDC; M&PR.
    - Beirne, Bryan; Pestology; Professor Emeriti, [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-247-1-17-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 830135-11, UNS 812.31-8.
    - Brooke, R.C., 1966; F-247-1-17-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Finlayson, Thelma; Professor Emeriti, 1965 - 1986; F-247-1-17-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 69013, UNS 86260.
    - Fisher, F.J. Fulton, 1966; F-247-1-17-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Geen, Glen H.; Dean of Science, [ca 1969] - [ca 1990]; F-247-1-17-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 69026; UNS 79121 [16].
    - Glen, I.R., 1969; F-247-1-17-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 69013.
    - Haver, Stoner, 1969; F-247-1-17-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Mackauer, J.P.M., 1969; F-247-1-17-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 69026.
    - Nair, K.; Professor Emeriti, 1969; F-247-1-17-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Nelson, C. Donald; Dean of Science, 1966 - 1967; F-247-1-17-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; LIDC.
    - Sadleir, Dr. Richard Michael, 1969 - 1970; F-247-1-17-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC, M&PR, Comment.
    - Srivastava, Lalit; V.P. Academic, 1966 - 1988; F-247-1-17-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Schwarz, Abby; Visiting Professor, 1975; F-247-1-17-0-14 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: M Comment.
    - Turnbull, A.; Professor Emeriti, 1969; F-247-1-17-0-15 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Turner, John; Visiting Professor, University of Sydney, 1969; F-247-1-17-0-16 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 69026.
    - VanEerton, G., 1966; F-247-1-17-0-17 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - VanOverbeek, A.P., 1966; F-247-1-17-0-18 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Vidaver, William; Professor Emeriti, 1966 - 1981; F-247-1-17-0-19 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; 69026, IMC.
  - Chemistry, 1965 - 1988; F-247-1-18; 7 cm of textual records 118 photographs 24 contact sheets 1 negative
    Sub-series consists of photos, articles, and published material relating to individuals from the Department of Chemistry. For a list of faculty members associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Aronoff, Sam; Bell, Tom N.; Benet, A.; Kasteling; Borgford; Tomason; Chow, Joe; Chow, Y.L.; Cornell, Rosemary; Cushley, Bob; D'Auria, John; Einstein, Fred; Funt, B. Lionel; Gay, Ian; Gressor, Mike; Hill, Ross; Jones, Colin H. W.; Kiehlmann, Eberhard; Korteling, R.G.; Lower, Steven K.; Malli, Gulzari; Meakin, Denys; Oehlschlager, Cam; Pate, Brian D.; Percival, Paul; Peterson, Louis; Pinto, Mario; Pomeroy, Roland; Sherwood, Alden; Slessor, Keith; Sutton, Derek; Tracey, Alan; Tuck, D. G.; Unrau, A.M.; Voight, Eva; Walkley, John; Wells, Edward J.; Department of Chemistry; Richards, Bill
    - Aronoff, Samuel, [ca 1970] - [ca 1981]; F-247-1-18-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Bell, Tom, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88284.
    - Benet, A.; Borgford; Kasteling; Tomason, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC?.
    - Chow, Joe, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88278.
    - Chow, Y.L., [ca 1988]; F-247-1-18-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Cornell, Rosemary, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88282.
    - Cushley, Bob, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88285.
    - D'Auria, John, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Einstein, Fred, 1969 - 1988; F-247-1-18-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 69026; 88281/7.
    - Funt, Lionel; Dean of Science, [ca 1970] - [ca 1988]; F-247-1-18-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88283.
    - Gay, Ian, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Gressor, Mike, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88280.
    - Hill, Ross, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88289.
    - Jones, Colin, 1966 - 1988; F-247-1-18-0-14 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; 88291.
    - Kiehlmann, Eberhard, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-15 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88288.
    - Korteling, R.G., [ca 1966] - [ca 1988]; F-247-1-18-0-16 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; 69026; 88291.
    - Lower, Steve, 1966 - 1988; F-247-1-18-0-17 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Malli, Gulzari, 1969 - 1988; F-247-1-18-0-18 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Meakin, D., 1966; F-247-1-18-0-19 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Oehlschlager, Cam, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-20 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Pate, Brian D., 1966 - 1968; F-247-1-18-0-21 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; AV.
    - Percival, Paul, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-22 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Peterson, Louis, 1966 - 1988; F-247-1-18-0-23 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; 69013; 88290.
    - Pinto, Mario, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-24 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Pomeroy, Roland, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-25 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88287.
    - Richards, Bill, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-26 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88286.
    - Sherwood, Alden, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-27 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88292.
    - Slessor, Keith, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-28 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Sutton, Derek, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-29 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88290.
    - Tracey, Alan, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-30 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88279.
    - Tuck, D.G., 1966 - 1969; F-247-1-18-0-31 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; 69087.
    - Unrau, A.M.; Co-Op Education, 1965 - 1988; F-247-1-18-0-32 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Voight, Eva, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-33 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: 88294.
    - Walkley, John, 1988; F-247-1-18-0-34 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
    - Wells, E.J. (Ted), 1966 - 1988; F-247-1-18-0-35 (Archival box - standard 247-3)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; 88282.
  - Mathematics, 1966 - 1969; F-247-1-19; 2 cm of textual records 15 photographs 17 contact sheets
    Sub-series consists of photos of individuals from the Department of Mathematics. For a list of faculty members associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Chen, W.P.; Dirnberger, J.; Eaves, D.M.; Freedman, Allen R.; Gerber, Harvey; Harrop, Ronald; Lachlan, Alistair H.; Sember, J.; Department of Mathematics
    - Chen, W.P., 1966; F-247-1-19-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; Pacific Photographer.
    - Dirnberger, J.; Visiting Lecturer, 1969; F-247-1-19-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Eaves, D.M., 1966; F-247-1-19-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Freedman, A.R., 1966 - 1969; F-247-1-19-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; PPP; 69026.
    - Gerber, Harvey, 1966; F-247-1-19-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Harrop, Ronald, 1969; F-247-1-19-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Lachlan, A.H., 1966; F-247-1-19-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Sember, J., 1969; F-247-1-19-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Mathematics Faculty, [ca 1969]; F-247-1-19-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
  - Physics, 1964 - 1985; F-247-1-20; 3 cm of textual records 31 photographs 21 contact sheets
    Sub-series consists of photos, articles, and published material relating to individuals from the Department of Physics. For a list of faculty members associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Ballentyne, Leslie E.; Clayman, Bruce P.; Cochrane, John F.; Colbow, Konrad; Enns, Richard H.; Frindt, Robert F.; Haering, R. R.; Huntley, Dave J.; Irwin, J. Chuck; Jones, Billy; Rieckhoff, Klaus E.; Viswanathan, K.S.; Department of Physics
    - Ballentyne, Leslie E., 1969; F-247-1-20-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Clayman, Bruce; Dean of Graduate Studies, 1969 - 1985; F-247-1-20-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Cochran, John F., 1966; F-247-1-20-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Colbow, Konrad, 1966 - 1982; F-247-1-20-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Enns, Richard H., 1966 - 1969; F-247-1-20-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; 69026.
    - Frindt, R.F., 1966; F-247-1-20-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Haering, Rudy R.; V.P. Academic, 1964 - 1966; F-247-1-20-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Creator's original file classification code: Wilson Bros.; Helcermanas.
    - Huntley, Dave J., 1966; F-247-1-20-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Irwin, J. Chuck, 1966 - 1969; F-247-1-20-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Jones, Billy, 1969; F-247-1-20-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Rieckhoff, Klaus; Dean of Science, 1966 - 1969; F-247-1-20-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas, AVC.
    - Viswanathan, K.S., [ca 1966]; F-247-1-20-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Physics Faculty, [ca 1966]; F-247-1-20-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
  - Business Administration, 1976 - 1987; F-247-1-21; 9 cm of textual records 53 photographs
    Sub-series consists of photos, articles, curriculum vitae, and published material relating to individuals from the Faculty of Business Administration. For a list of faculty members associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Beedie School of Business
    Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release and, as a result of the review, access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
    - Faculty and Staff Members, [ca 1983]; F-247-1-21-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
    - Abdel-Magid, Moustafa; Accounting, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Abdel-Magid, Moustafa; Textual records
    - Alder, Roman, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Alder, Roman; Textual records
    - Andrews, Bob, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Andrews, Bob; Textual records
    - Brooking, Bryan; Management, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Brooking, Bryan; Textual records
    - Brown, Terrence; Accounting, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Brown, Terrence; Textual records
    - Cheng, Pao; Finance; Professor Emeriti, 1983 - 1987; F-247-1-21-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Cheng, Pao; Textual records
      Creator's original file classification code: UNS 87315-7.
    - Choo, Eng; Management Science, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Choo, Eng; Textual records
    - Etherington, Lois; Accounting, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Etherington, Lois; Textual records
    - Field, Richard; Organizational Behaviour, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Field, Richard; Textual records
    - Fleischer, Balt; Accounting, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Fleischer, Balt; Photographic materials
    - Globerman, Steve; Business, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Globerman, Steve; Textual records
    - Gordon, Irene; Accounting, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Gordon, Irene; Textual records
    - Grauer, Rob; Finance, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-14 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Grauer, Rob; Textual records
    - Herzog, John; Finance, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-15 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Herzog, John P.; Textual records
    - Holmes, Dick; Chair, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-16 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Holmes, Dick; Textual records
    - Hoyt, Cal; Dean of Business Administration, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-17 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Hoyt, George C.; Textual records
    - Iannacone, Ernie; Accounting, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-18 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Iannacone, Ernie; Textual records
    - Kendall, Ken; Marketing, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-19 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Kendall, Ken; Textual records
    - Kyle, John; Organizational Behaviour, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-20 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Kyle, John; Textual records
    - LeBon, Claude; Business Dean, 1985 - 1987; F-247-1-21-0-21 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      LeBon, Claude; Textual records
      Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Vol. 32, No. 8.
    - Mauser, Gary; Marketing, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-22 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Mauser, Gary; Textual records
    - McDonald, Dan; Accounting, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-23 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      McDonald, Dan; Textual records
    - McGill, Betty; Organizational Behaviour, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-24 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      McGill, Betty; Textual records
    - Meredith, Lindsay; Marketing, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-25 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Meredith, Lindsay N.; Textual records
    - Pinfeld, Larry; Organizational Behaviour, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-26 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Pinfeld, Larry; Textual records
    - Richards, John; Business, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-27 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Richards, John; Textual records
    - Rogow, Bob; Industrial Relations, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-28 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Rogow, Robert; Textual records
    - Ross, Jerry; Organizational Behaviour, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-29 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Ross, Jerry; Textual records
    - Schachter, Barry; Finance, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-30 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Schachter, Barry; Textual records
    - Schoner, Bert; Marketing, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-31 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Schoner, Bertram; Textual records
    - Schwindt, Richard; Industrial Organization, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-32 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Schwindt, Richard; Textual records
    - Shalchi, Hossein; Accounting, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-33 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Shalchi, Hossein; Textual records
    - Shapiro, Stan; Dean of Business Administration, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-34 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Shapiro, Stanley; Textual records
    - Smart, Carolyne; Business Policy, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-35 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Smart, Carolyne F.; Textual records
    - Stark, Marvin; Commercial Law, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-36 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Stark, Marvin; Textual records
    - Tjosvold, Dean; Organizational Behaviour, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-37 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Tjosvold, Dean; Textual records
    - Trifonidis, Beverly; Accounting, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-38 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Trifonidis, Beverly; Textual records
    - Triplett, Leslie; Director, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-39 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Triplett, Leslie; Textual records
    - Var, Turgut; Accounting, 1976 - 1987; F-247-1-21-0-40 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Var, Turgut; Textual records
      Pending review
    - Vergin, Roger; Operations Research, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-41 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Vergin, Roger; Textual records
    - Wedley, Bill; MBA Program, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-42 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Wedley, William C.; Textual records
    - Wexler, Max; Business, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-43 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Wexler, Max; Textual records
    - Woolley, Peter; Accounting, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-44 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Woolley, Peter; Textual records
    - Wycham, Bob; Marketing, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-45 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Wycham, Bob; Textual records
    - Zaki, Ahmed; Management Information Systems, 1983; F-247-1-21-0-46 (Archival box - standard 247-4)
      Zaki, Ahmed; Textual records
  - Education, 1965 - 1991; F-247-1-22; 13 cm of textual records 86 photographs 61 contact sheets 6 negatives
    Sub-series consists of photos, contact sheets, articles, and published material relating to individuals from the Faculty of Education. For a list of faculty members associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Birch, Daniel R.; Attridge, B. F.; Borsos, Bob; Cant, Margaret; Cooke, Barry; Dawson, A.J. (Sandy); Day, Jim; Eastwood, Gordon R.; Egan, Kieran; Elliott, Arthur; Ellis, John F.; Garland, Iris; Gelbach, Roger; Gibbons, Maurice; Harper, Robert J.C.; Hayward, F. Margaret; Hood, K.H.; Hunter, Adrienne; Ivany, J. W. George; Jones, Robert; Kazepides, Anastasios; Kirchner, Glenn; Kootnekoff, J.L.; MacKinnon, Archie R.; Martin, Jack; McClaren, Milton; O'Connell, M. Sheila; Prock, Leone; Robinson, Norman; Sandvoss, Joachim; Savage, Paul; Shapson, Stanley M.; Stratton, Stephen; Trivett, John; Tuinman, Jaap J.; Walker, Tom; Wassermann, Selma; Whitney, Al; Wideen, Marvin F.; Wyatt, Jane; Faculty of Education
    - Education Faculty, 1965 - 1979; F-247-1-22-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Attridge, B.F.; Chair, Communication Centre, 1966; F-247-1-22-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Birch, Daniel; Dean, Assistant V.P. Academic, 1971; F-247-1-22-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Borsos, Bob, 1979; F-247-1-22-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79052-31.
    - Cant, Margaret; Physical Development Centre, 1966; F-247-1-22-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas, PPP.
    - Cooke, Barry, 1979; F-247-1-22-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79056-9.
    - Dawson, Sandy, 1979; F-247-1-22-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79054-19.
    - Day, Jim, 1966; F-247-1-22-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Eastwood, Gordon, [ca 1966]; F-247-1-22-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: Steve Peterson.
    - Egan, Kieran, 1979; F-247-1-22-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79052-26.
    - Elliott, Arthur, 1979; F-247-1-22-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79052-28.
    - Ellis, John; Chair, Educational Foundation Centre; Dean, also Professor Emeriti, 1969 - 1973; F-247-1-22-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: AVC 1-4-69, LIDC 73012-5.
    - Garland, Iris; Physical Development Centre, Centre for Arts, 1966; F-247-1-22-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Gelbach, Roger, 1979; F-247-1-22-0-14 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79056-11.
    - Gibbons, Maurice; also Professor Emeriti, 1979; F-247-1-22-0-15 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79053-9, 79039-3.
    - Harper, R.J.C.; Educational Foundations Centre, 1966; F-247-1-22-0-16 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Hayward, F. Margaret G.; Communication Centre, 1966; F-247-1-22-0-17 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Hood, K.H.; Physical Development Centre, Assistant Football Coach, 1965; F-247-1-22-0-18 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Hunter, Adrienne, 1966; F-247-1-22-0-19 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Ivany, J.W.G.; Dean of Education, V.P. Academic, 1983; F-247-1-22-0-20 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79053-14; UNS 83-1-2.
    - Jones, Robert; Director, Learning Resources Centre, 1982 - 1983; F-247-1-22-0-21 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week Vol. 22, No. 11.
    - Kazepides, Anastasios, [ca 1983]; F-247-1-22-0-22 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Kirchner, Glenn; Physical Development Centre, also Professor Emeriti, 1965 - [ca 1989]; F-247-1-22-0-23 (Archival box - standard 247-5)